{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993418601","data":{"timestamp":" 946993418601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993423253","data":{"timestamp":" 946993423252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993423411","data":{"timestamp":" 946993423411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993428524","data":{"timestamp":" 946993428524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993429205","data":{"timestamp":" 946993429205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993434364","data":{"timestamp":" 946993434364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993437063","data":{"timestamp":" 946993437063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993442262","data":{"timestamp":" 946993442262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993443865","data":{"timestamp":" 946993443865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993447772","data":{"timestamp":" 946993447771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993452144","data":{"timestamp":" 946993452144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993453598","data":{"timestamp":" 946993453598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993454206","data":{"timestamp":" 946993454206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993457151","data":{"timestamp":" 946993457150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993468414","data":{"timestamp":" 946993468414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993473392","data":{"timestamp":" 946993473392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993477067","data":{"timestamp":" 946993477067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993481028","data":{"timestamp":" 946993481027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993485085","data":{"timestamp":" 946993485085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993489508","data":{"timestamp":" 946993489507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993494113","data":{"timestamp":" 946993494112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993496316","data":{"timestamp":" 946993496316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993498505","data":{"timestamp":" 946993498505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993500298","data":{"timestamp":" 946993500298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993504470","data":{"timestamp":" 946993504470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993507432","data":{"timestamp":" 946993507431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993516104","data":{"timestamp":" 946993516104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" b420107a-fa12-497e-8677-9b58f3e2073f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993545138","data":{"timestamp":" 946993545138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 448a0bc1-4fad-41ff-8a0c-5591cafad822"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993554374","data":{"timestamp":" 946993554373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 448a0bc1-4fad-41ff-8a0c-5591cafad822"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993559409","data":{"timestamp":" 946993559409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 448a0bc1-4fad-41ff-8a0c-5591cafad822"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993564666","data":{"timestamp":" 946993564666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 448a0bc1-4fad-41ff-8a0c-5591cafad822"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993571656","data":{"timestamp":" 946993571656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 448a0bc1-4fad-41ff-8a0c-5591cafad822"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993578965","data":{"timestamp":" 946993578965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 448a0bc1-4fad-41ff-8a0c-5591cafad822"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993583942","data":{"timestamp":" 946993583942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 448a0bc1-4fad-41ff-8a0c-5591cafad822"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993589551","data":{"timestamp":" 946993589551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 448a0bc1-4fad-41ff-8a0c-5591cafad822"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993594813","data":{"timestamp":" 946993594813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 448a0bc1-4fad-41ff-8a0c-5591cafad822"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993602808","data":{"timestamp":" 946993602808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 448a0bc1-4fad-41ff-8a0c-5591cafad822"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993627243","data":{"timestamp":" 946993627243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993631772","data":{"timestamp":" 946993631772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993634194","data":{"timestamp":" 946993634194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993638075","data":{"timestamp":" 946993638075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993641077","data":{"timestamp":" 946993641077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993648712","data":{"timestamp":" 946993648712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993654196","data":{"timestamp":" 946993654196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993657118","data":{"timestamp":" 946993657118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993659607","data":{"timestamp":" 946993659607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993665934","data":{"timestamp":" 946993665934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993671207","data":{"timestamp":" 946993671207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993676936","data":{"timestamp":" 946993676936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993680600","data":{"timestamp":" 946993680600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993685085","data":{"timestamp":" 946993685084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993687871","data":{"timestamp":" 946993687870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993690275","data":{"timestamp":" 946993690275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993701210","data":{"timestamp":" 946993701210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993712490","data":{"timestamp":" 946993712490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993721341","data":{"timestamp":" 946993721341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 9073dc86-3ba2-4859-8baa-21b34c2228c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993747409","data":{"timestamp":" 946993747408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 728f0951-6be3-43be-a312-e1aed9667a69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993750359","data":{"timestamp":" 946993750359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 728f0951-6be3-43be-a312-e1aed9667a69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993757326","data":{"timestamp":" 946993757326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 728f0951-6be3-43be-a312-e1aed9667a69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993762090","data":{"timestamp":" 946993762090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 728f0951-6be3-43be-a312-e1aed9667a69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993767209","data":{"timestamp":" 946993767209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 728f0951-6be3-43be-a312-e1aed9667a69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993768037","data":{"timestamp":" 946993768037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 728f0951-6be3-43be-a312-e1aed9667a69"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993784476","data":{"timestamp":" 946993784476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993787086","data":{"timestamp":" 946993787086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993790806","data":{"timestamp":" 946993790806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993797114","data":{"timestamp":" 946993797114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993798436","data":{"timestamp":" 946993798436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993804502","data":{"timestamp":" 946993804501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993806496","data":{"timestamp":" 946993806496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993811618","data":{"timestamp":" 946993811618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993813325","data":{"timestamp":" 946993813325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993818520","data":{"timestamp":" 946993818520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993819647","data":{"timestamp":" 946993819647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993821793","data":{"timestamp":" 946993821793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993825850","data":{"timestamp":" 946993825849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993827525","data":{"timestamp":" 946993827525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993829836","data":{"timestamp":" 946993829836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993830941","data":{"timestamp":" 946993830941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993831081","data":{"timestamp":" 946993831081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993836129","data":{"timestamp":" 946993836124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993837161","data":{"timestamp":" 946993837161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993838794","data":{"timestamp":" 946993838794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993843979","data":{"timestamp":" 946993843979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993844688","data":{"timestamp":" 946993844688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993846539","data":{"timestamp":" 946993846539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993846870","data":{"timestamp":" 946993846870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993849771","data":{"timestamp":" 946993849771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993850373","data":{"timestamp":" 946993850372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993852445","data":{"timestamp":" 946993852445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993853329","data":{"timestamp":" 946993853329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993855591","data":{"timestamp":" 946993855591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993856007","data":{"timestamp":" 946993856007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993857916","data":{"timestamp":" 946993857916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993863133","data":{"timestamp":" 946993863133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993865017","data":{"timestamp":" 946993865017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993867550","data":{"timestamp":" 946993867550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993870923","data":{"timestamp":" 946993870923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993872546","data":{"timestamp":" 946993872546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993873800","data":{"timestamp":" 946993873800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993875238","data":{"timestamp":" 946993875238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993877740","data":{"timestamp":" 946993877740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993879850","data":{"timestamp":" 946993879849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993880406","data":{"timestamp":" 946993880406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993882564","data":{"timestamp":" 946993882564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993884213","data":{"timestamp":" 946993884213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993885035","data":{"timestamp":" 946993885035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 24"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993886192","data":{"timestamp":" 946993886192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 24"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993891329","data":{"timestamp":" 946993891329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 25"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993894519","data":{"timestamp":" 946993894518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 25"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993905540","data":{"timestamp":" 946993905540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 25"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993916644","data":{"timestamp":" 946993916643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 25"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993917146","data":{"timestamp":" 946993917146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" a8e7e752-fc3c-4bc8-9a9e-b0d86d763c7a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993935945","data":{"timestamp":" 946993935945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993940431","data":{"timestamp":" 946993940430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993945030","data":{"timestamp":" 946993945029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993948769","data":{"timestamp":" 946993948769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993954829","data":{"timestamp":" 946993954829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993959105","data":{"timestamp":" 946993959105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993962271","data":{"timestamp":" 946993962271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993967894","data":{"timestamp":" 946993967894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993970529","data":{"timestamp":" 946993970529"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993973111","data":{"timestamp":" 946993973110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993976022","data":{"timestamp":" 946993976022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993985115","data":{"timestamp":" 946993985115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993988757","data":{"timestamp":" 946993988757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993994078","data":{"timestamp":" 946993994078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993996718","data":{"timestamp":" 946993996718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993999821","data":{"timestamp":" 946993999821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994001921","data":{"timestamp":" 946994001921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994006176","data":{"timestamp":" 946994006175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994009798","data":{"timestamp":" 946994009798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994012984","data":{"timestamp":" 946994012984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994016939","data":{"timestamp":" 946994016938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 24"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994019654","data":{"timestamp":" 946994019654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 25"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.copy.ltr:story_2.noerror.2.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994030698","data":{"timestamp":" 946994030697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" f230505a-fc26-4849-9f0f-d88917ff3001"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.copy.ltr_story_2.noerror.2.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994040589","data":{"timestamp":" 946994040588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1f220916-ee09-41a0-a157-aa805d550e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994040819","data":{"timestamp":" 946994040819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1f220916-ee09-41a0-a157-aa805d550e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994041792","data":{"timestamp":" 946994041791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1f220916-ee09-41a0-a157-aa805d550e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994043077","data":{"timestamp":" 946994043077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1f220916-ee09-41a0-a157-aa805d550e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994045980","data":{"timestamp":" 946994045980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1f220916-ee09-41a0-a157-aa805d550e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994046559","data":{"timestamp":" 946994046559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1f220916-ee09-41a0-a157-aa805d550e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994046658","data":{"timestamp":" 946994046658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1f220916-ee09-41a0-a157-aa805d550e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994064437","data":{"timestamp":" 946994064437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" defab482-2b66-46ed-b9d5-2008eba2ad20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994072755","data":{"timestamp":" 946994072754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" defab482-2b66-46ed-b9d5-2008eba2ad20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994079658","data":{"timestamp":" 946994079657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" defab482-2b66-46ed-b9d5-2008eba2ad20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994100829","data":{"timestamp":" 946994100829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" defab482-2b66-46ed-b9d5-2008eba2ad20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994120886","data":{"timestamp":" 946994120886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" e45ee8e4-52a3-4ae4-ae60-f8167a48a092"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994130445","data":{"timestamp":" 946994130444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" e45ee8e4-52a3-4ae4-ae60-f8167a48a092"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994138271","data":{"timestamp":" 946994138271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" e45ee8e4-52a3-4ae4-ae60-f8167a48a092"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994155659","data":{"timestamp":" 946994155658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" e45ee8e4-52a3-4ae4-ae60-f8167a48a092"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994163981","data":{"timestamp":" 946994163981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" e45ee8e4-52a3-4ae4-ae60-f8167a48a092"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994184263","data":{"timestamp":" 946994184262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" d20a1074-1971-4ba7-b495-023ff3473960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994193700","data":{"timestamp":" 946994193700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" d20a1074-1971-4ba7-b495-023ff3473960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994202840","data":{"timestamp":" 946994202839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" d20a1074-1971-4ba7-b495-023ff3473960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994208606","data":{"timestamp":" 946994208606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" d20a1074-1971-4ba7-b495-023ff3473960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994214058","data":{"timestamp":" 946994214058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" d20a1074-1971-4ba7-b495-023ff3473960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994221923","data":{"timestamp":" 946994221923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" d20a1074-1971-4ba7-b495-023ff3473960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994228598","data":{"timestamp":" 946994228598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" d20a1074-1971-4ba7-b495-023ff3473960"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994250164","data":{"timestamp":" 946994250164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" bf73ad6c-c4c4-4b8b-9be3-4a852616abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994255806","data":{"timestamp":" 946994255805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" bf73ad6c-c4c4-4b8b-9be3-4a852616abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994266009","data":{"timestamp":" 946994266009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" bf73ad6c-c4c4-4b8b-9be3-4a852616abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994273085","data":{"timestamp":" 946994273084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" bf73ad6c-c4c4-4b8b-9be3-4a852616abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994279212","data":{"timestamp":" 946994279212"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" bf73ad6c-c4c4-4b8b-9be3-4a852616abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994286925","data":{"timestamp":" 946994286925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" bf73ad6c-c4c4-4b8b-9be3-4a852616abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994291594","data":{"timestamp":" 946994291586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" bf73ad6c-c4c4-4b8b-9be3-4a852616abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994304087","data":{"timestamp":" 946994304086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" bf73ad6c-c4c4-4b8b-9be3-4a852616abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947003100582","data":{"timestamp":" 947003100582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" bf73ad6c-c4c4-4b8b-9be3-4a852616abac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947003122942","data":{"timestamp":" 947003122941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1bc95401-3281-4055-8dc3-e108de009ea7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947003132425","data":{"timestamp":" 947003132424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1bc95401-3281-4055-8dc3-e108de009ea7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947003139450","data":{"timestamp":" 947003139450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1bc95401-3281-4055-8dc3-e108de009ea7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947003166278","data":{"timestamp":" 947003166278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1bc95401-3281-4055-8dc3-e108de009ea7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947003176169","data":{"timestamp":" 947003176168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 1bc95401-3281-4055-8dc3-e108de009ea7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947003198078","data":{"timestamp":" 947003198077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 5cd781a4-6bbf-451d-8d36-b0db3b621df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim:story_1.cap.1.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947003207647","data":{"timestamp":" 947003207647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_164312"," gameId":" 5cd781a4-6bbf-451d-8d36-b0db3b621df6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.nostim_story_1.cap.1.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"end":"end"}]}